- access.lua: which will contain the code logic that does the job (i.e. adding the header « Hello-World » to the response)
- handler.lua: which will declare our plugin « HelloWorld »
- schema.lua: which will contain the configuration schema of our plugin. This schema will define the different configuration parameters supported by our plugin and their type (string, array, number, etc.). This schema will be used by Kong to store our plugin configuration into Cassandra and validate any update of the configuration